<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Lim Yu Zher's Online Resume</title><link>https://lzher385.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Lim Yu Zher's Online Resume</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lzher385.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ninja Scheduler</title><link>https://lzher385.github.io/projects/creations/ninjascheduler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 04:38:08 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://lzher385.github.io/projects/creations/ninjascheduler/</guid><description>Description Ninja Scheduler is the bot designed for busy people who are unavailable to receive their package on the actual delivery day. This bot is targeted at customers who might be unavailable to receive the package on the stipulated delivery date, and might want to reschedule the delivery. It is also designed for users who are willing to pay more to get faster deliveries, but are unable to do so as online retailers often only offer the cheapest (and thus slowest) delivery option.</description></item><item><title>gitGud</title><link>https://lzher385.github.io/projects/creations/gitgud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 04:22:56 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://lzher385.github.io/projects/creations/gitgud/</guid><description>Description gitGud is a desktop application for storing and managing your friends&amp;rsquo; gaming information and schedules. It is dedicated to gamers like you and provides a gamer-themed experience with a focus on increasing your efficiency through its typing-based interface.
Previously, keeping track of all of yours friends&amp;rsquo; gaming information and schedules can be difficult and time-consuming. However, with gitGud, there is no need to get tilted (frustrated) by this anymore as gitGud provides you with a convenient platform to manage essential gaming information of your fellow gamer friends.</description></item></channel></rss>